Contact

dmaddy611@me.com

www.linkedin.com/in/davidmaddy (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Non-profit Board Development Account Management Nursing Education

Languages

French (Elementary)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Limited Working)

Honors-Awards

Nurse Corps Scholarship Program Scholars Award

National Account Manager of the Year HD Supply

Volunteer of the Year, Stepping Stone San Diego

Professional Achievement Award Leadership for Results

David Maddy

Registered Nurse, BSN, PHN San Diego

Summary

As an Emergency Room RN, I work providing patient care at Kaiser San Diego Zion and SDMC Hospitals. I also care for patients as a per diem member of the Sonata Hospice team.

I studied overseas during high school developing both a love of travel & the zeal to explore our diverse world. Before earning my BSN in 2013 from National University, I earned a BA in Psychology from the University of Kansas in 1992.

Working as a National Account Manager for Home Depot for nearly 10 years, I developed my passion for environmentalism. Eventually joining their Green Team, focusing on energy efficiency solutions and environmentally friendly alternatives for my customers.

I volunteer for several non-profit organizations in San Diego where I have lived for the past 20 years. I have worked on Development in Gardening (DIG) projects in Uganda, Kenya, and Tanzania. I am an Advisory Board Member for DIG.

I cherish spending time outdoors enjoying nature and I am a passionate photographer. Some of my photos have been displayed at DIG fundraisers & also published in the CDC's "Yellow Book" and international travel brochures.

Experience

Kaiser Permanente
5 years 5 months
Emergency Room Nurse
March 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Emergency Room Registered Nurse April 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months) San Diego, California

Page 1 of 4

Registered Nurse

April 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months)

San Diego, California

Emergency room Registered Nurse

Registered Nurse

March 2015 - Present (5 years 5 months)

Enjoying working on the Medical-Surgical floors delivering exceptional care.

Sonata Hospice

Registered Nurse

March 2015 - Present (5 years 5 months)

El Centro Regional Medical Center

ER Registered Nurse

July 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 3 months)

El Centro, California

Paradise Valley Hospital

Emergency Services RN

February 2014 - January 2015 (1 year)

Ardent Hospice and Palliative Care

Per Diem RN

January 2014 - January 2015 (1 year 1 month)

Development in Gardening

Volunteer

2008 - 2014 (6 years)

National University

BSN Student Nurse

January 2012 - November 2013 (1 year 11 months)

San Diego, CA

CLINICAL EXPERIENCE

Assessment, Casa de las Capanas Assisted Living 137 hours

Fundamentals, Villas de las Palmas Healthcare 137 hours

Medical-Surgical Nursing, telemetry, oncology, & neurology

Kaiser Permanente Medical Center 254 hours

Intensive Care Unit, Kaiser Medical Center 12 hours

Emergency Department, Kaiser Medical Center 8 hours

Labor & Delivery, Scripps Mercy 137 hours

Pediatrics, Kaiser Permanente Medical Center 137 hours

Psychiatric Nursing, Scripps Mercy 137 hours

Community & Public Health Nursing 142 hours

Leadership, Scripps Memorial 137 hours

International Service Learning

Volunteer Nursing Student

December 2012 - January 2013 (2 months)

Community health work in poor neighborhoods as a part of an ISL community triage team

accompanying hospital nursing faculty and receiving hands on training.

Assessment of patients' vital signs.

Performed patient interviews/intake at village triage clinics.

Observed and participated in supervised labor and delivery duties.

Assisted with administrative procedures.

Participated in a clinical rotation in a local hospital.

Monitoring and caring for diabetic patients.

Assisted in antiparasitic screenings and treatments.

Performed blood and urine testing.

Provided educational presentations to community.

Observed surgeries, including C-sections.

Basic pharmacology training and assisting with pharmacy at clinics.

Attended a natural medicines seminar.

Tropical disease training (malaria, dengue, etc.)

Performed basic pediatric ear/eye/nose/throat exam.

Environmental medical surveying.

Learn the practice and history of indigenous medical techniques and medicines.

Practice medical Spanish.

HD Supply National Account Manager 2000 - 2009 (9 years)

San Diego, CA

Managed National Accounts within the lodging industry. Driving sales with exceptional service and attention to detail. Using both strategic sales and large account management training to move through the sales process and negotiate agreements. Exceeded sales plan objectives and part margin goals.

Elected to the Advisory Board for Vantage Hospitality serving for five years as their vendor representative. Recognized as the National Account Manager of the Year in 2003 and in 2007.

Education

University of Kansas Bachelor's degree, Psychology · (1986 - 1992)

National University
BSN, Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2013)

National University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse